## atul chavan

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Sr. Dot net developer at Reliance Communication.

## Summary

Experienced Deputy Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the telecommunications industry. Skilled in Windows Communication Foundation (WCF), Web Api, Entity framework, ADO.NET, XML, JavaScript, and ASP.NET. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor of Engineering focused in Computer Engineering from Pune University.

### Experience

Sr - Dot net developer at RELIANCE TECH SERVICES LIMITED

December 2015 - Present (2 years 7 months)

Sr. Software Developer at Reliance General Insurance

October 2014 - December 2015 (1 year 3 months)

Web Base Application, c#.net, WCF,asp.net, sql server 2008, xml, Javascript

Asp.net, Wcf, Sql server Developer at Market place technology, Belapur

January 2013 - October 2014 (1 year 10 months)

Asp.net with vb.net and sql server 2008. (Web base and Windows Base both)

Projects: 1) Dmat (Web based) asp.net, Sql Server 2008.

- 2) Dmat Mailer (Windows based).dot net,
- 3) Daily task Activity (Web base) Asp.net, WCF, sql server 2008
- 4) Citrus (Web Base) Asp.net, Sql Server 2008.

#### Worked as software Programmer at Windfall Enterprises

February 2012 - December 2012 (11 months)

Worked under e-Recruit project which is developed with Asp.net, javascript, xml, C#, sql server 2008.

software developer in Dot net at Microstop infotech pvt ltd.

January 2011 - January 2012 (1 year 1 month)

ERP Developed in Asp.net with Oracle 9i.

## Education

Amruvahini college of engg.. sangamner computer engg, 2007 - 2010

Pune University
Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Engineering, 2007 - 2010
MSBTE
Diploma, ComputerEngineering, 2004 - 2007

## atul chavan

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Sr. Dot net developer at Reliance Communication.

# Linked in Recruiter

Profile Notes and Activity (1)

6/15/2018—View by Vikram Kumar